Clara E. Sipprell Papers
Clara E. Sipprell Papers
- Negatives and proof prints
  - Cleary, Miss Dorothy, 1960
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Cleghorn, Sally, picnic over against Brun Peak
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)
  - Clement, Mrs. E.D., 1944
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
  - Clerett, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB092)
  - Cloisters, Columbia University
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
    - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - Negatives (Box 49)
  - Clummings, Cornelia
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
  - Cobb, Margaret Ayer, 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
  - Cody, Regina
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Coff, Margaret Ayer, 1958
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)
  - Cohen, Nathan
    - Negatives (Box FB092)
  - Cole, Mrs. Marshall (3 daughters)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Cole, Timothy
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Comfort, Barbara, 1961
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
  - Conistork, Mrs. George E. (grandchildren Bunny, Louis, Sally; 635 College Street, Beloit, WI
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Connaway, Mr. and Mrs. Jay, 1964
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Connolly, Mrs. Leo, 1961
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
  - Constantine, Maria
    - Negatives (Box FB092)
  - Constantinople (Istanbul)
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
  - Constantinople (Rome, Florence, Luzerne)
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
  - Consuela
    - Negatives (Box FB092)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Cook, George Jr.
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Cooley, Mrs. Roger G. and children Linda and Nancy, 1945
    - Negatives (Box FB092)
  - Coolidge, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
  - Cordley, Mrs. C.M.
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
  - Cornell, 1971
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Cortissoz, Royal
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
  - Coss, Mr. John
    - Negatives (Box FB092)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Costella, Barden J., 1970
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Cotton, Deborah
    - Negatives (Box FB092)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Covered bridges
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
  - Cowles, Mrs. Thornberg (Kate & Pat)
    - Negatives (Box FB092)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Coxe, Mrs. Alfred
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Coyle, Katherine
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Coyle, Kathleen, 1945
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
  - Craig, Mrs. Clayton B. (Ohio)
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Cram, Ralph Adams, chapel in Sudbury, MA, Aug 1936
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Crane, Mr. Cornelius (Miri Rei Tahitian)
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
  - Crater
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
  - Crawford, Prof. Franzo, 1964
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Cressy, Elanor (daughter of Mr. and Mrs. George Cressy), before marriage
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
  - Cressy, Mrs. George B., 1957
    See also Chatfield, Mrs. (mother of Mrs. George B. Cressy).
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
  - Crothers, Dr. Samuel
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
  - Cummings, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
  - Cummings, Jane (daughter of Ruth Percy)
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Cummins, Dr. (father in law of Mrs. T.R. Cummins), 1956
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Cummins, Mrs. T.R. and son Douglas, 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
  - Cummins, Mrs. Thomas R. Sr., 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Cuniberti, Mrs. Fernando (of Washington) with family
    - Negatives (Box FB013)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Cunningham, Mrs. G.E. (daughter of Mrs. Ritsher, 214 Forest Park Blvd, Jamesville, WI)
    - Negatives (Box FB014)
  - Cunningham, Mrs. S.L. (604 W. 112th St)
    - Negatives (Box FB014)
  - Currier, Betty
    - Negatives (Box FB014)
  - Currier, Mrs. R.J. (2 young children)
    - Negatives (Box FB014)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Currier, Mrs. Richard
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Curtis, Helen
    See also Perry, ---- (mother of Helen Perry Curtis).
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
  - Curtis, Helen (nephews and niece)
    - Negatives (Box FB014)
  - Curtis, Jean and Polly, 1926
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB014)
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Curtis, Jeanne
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Curtis, John and Helen and family, 1927
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Curtis, John M.
    - Negatives (Box FB188)
  - Curtis, Mrs. John (Jean and family)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Curtis, Polly, 1942
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Cushing, ---- (daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Cutler, Mrs. Gerald, 1969
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
  - Dallas, Dr. John
    - Negatives (Box FB188)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Dalton, D.
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Dana, Dr. Charles and John Cotton Dana
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
  - [Dana, Charles] Garden of Dr. Charles Dana, and portraits of Mr. Jo Dana
    - Negatives (Box FB022)
  - Dancing
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
  - Dargan, Mrs. Olive (West Ashville, NC, Balsam Ave, "Fielding Burice," pier name)
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
  - Darling Place
    - Negatives (Box FB094)
  - Dartmouth College Library
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
  - Davids, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Davis, E., 1969
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Davis, Mr. George H.
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Davis, Mrs. George
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Davis, Mrs. Rhoda (mother)
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - Davy, Kitty
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
  - Dawon, -----, 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Dawson School For Children
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - Dawson, Mr. & Mrs. and family, 1936
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Dawson, Theron J. and family, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Day, Clarence (Woodstock)
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Day, Susan Ann (Mrs. M.M. Day's [daughter])
    - Negatives (Box FB093)
    - Negatives (Box FB094)
  - de Angeli, Mrs. John, 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - De Augle, Marguerite, 1966
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
  - De Quintal, Mrs. E.A.
    - Negatives (Box FB094)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Dean, Vira M.
    - Negatives (Box FB094)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Deane, Marion
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Dearsa, Lt. W.U. and family
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Deaves, Marion C. (Diane?)
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
  - DeBevoise, Mrs. Robert L., 1961
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
  - DeForest, ---- (son in law)
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
  - DeForest, Anna and son
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
  - DeForest, Henry and daughter May, DeForest wedding
    - Negatives (Box FB094)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - DeForest, Mr. and Mrs. Henry L.
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - DeForest, Mrs. Henry, 1937
    - Negatives (Box FB095)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - DeForest, Mrs. Henry (Webster family), 1939
    - Negatives (Box FB095)
    - Negatives (Box FB096)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - DeForest, Mr. Johnston at daugher Priscilla's wedding
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
  - DeForest, Miss Mary
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
  - DeForest, Mrs., 1948
    - Negatives (Box FB094)
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - DeForest, Mary Payne and children
    See also Payne, Mary DeForest (son).
    - Negatives (Box FB094)
  - DeForest, Mrs. and Mrs. Oliver H. Payne (West Neck road, Cold Spring Harbor, L.I.), 1939
    - Negatives (Box FB094)
    - Negatives (Box FB095)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - DeForest, Robert W.
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
  - Denmark, Phyllis barn
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
  - Dewey, Dr. Godfrey
    - Negatives (Box FB096)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Dewey, Mrs. Godfrey, 1960
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
  - Dewey, Dr. John
    - Negatives (Box FB016)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Dexter, Caroline
    - Negatives (Box FB096)
  - Deykarhanova, Tamara, See Gabahan, Halen, and Tamara Deykarhanova.
  - Dickson, Carol, 1942
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Negatives (Box FB096)
  - Dickson, E.R.
    - Negatives (Box FB188)
  - Dickson, Edward R.
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Didisheim, Mrs. M.
    - Negatives (Box FB096)
  - Dillingham, Miss Louisa
    - Negatives (Box FB096)
  - Dimitrieff, Nicolas
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
  - Dimond, Mrs. Harriet
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Dippel, Mr. John H., 1960
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Dixter, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB188)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Dodge, Frank, 1932
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
  - Dodge, Mary Alice
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
  - Dodge-Whitefield, Frank
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
  - Donty, Anne, 1939
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Dorland, Mrs., 1950
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Dorland, Mrs R.C.
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
  - Dorset, Elizabeth Lee
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
  - Dorset, Miss Kandael
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - Dow, Arthur M.
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Dowd, Margaret, 1940
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
  - Down, Commander Hall and son Hall
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Downes, Anne Miller
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
  - Downs, Mrs. E.H. and son Hall (Hampton)
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Das, Dr. Taraknath
    - Negatives (Box FB094)
  - Draper, Mrs. William
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Drevenstedt Hoy, Avery [empty folder]
  - DuBois, W.E.B.
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - Dumond, Frank Vincent
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Dunbar, Mrs. Charles E. (daughter of Mrs. Jelley)
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
  - Dunbar, ---- (Mrs. John L. Dunbar's baby)
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Dunn, Eilene
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Dunn, Mr.
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Dunn, Mrs. Fayette, 1960
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
  - Dunning, Mrs. Davis
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
  - Duryea, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Dyson, ---- (mother of Miss Rose Dyson), 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
  - Eagan, Mrs. Walter
    - Negatives (Box FB097)
  - Eagan, Mrs. Walter H.
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Eagan, Walter W.
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Eaton, Mrs. Mar, 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Eckblom, Mr. John O.
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Eckstein, Gustav
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB100)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - Eddy, Kate
    - Negatives (Box FB018)
  - Eddy, Mrs. Henry S.
    - Negatives (Box FB098)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Edward, Mrs. Stanley (Miss Edward)
    - Negatives (Box FB188)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Edwards, Mrs. (Hartford)
    - Negatives (Box FB188)
  - Eichin, Margaret Follins ([daughter?] Addie), 1934
    - Negatives (Box FB099)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Eicks, Mrs. Charles
    - Negatives (Box FB098)
  - Einstein, Albert
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB098)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - Einstein, Albert with Konenkov
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - Einstein, Albert and son in law [Dmitri] Marianoff
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB098)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - Eiser, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB018)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Ekbom, Mr. and Mrs. Jack, 1956
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB018)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Eldh, Carl, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB018)
  - Eldredge, Mary, 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB018)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Eldredge, Stuart
    - Negatives (Box FB018)
  - Eldredge, Stuart (bride), 1965
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Electra, Arthur
    - Negatives (Box FB080)
  - Elinch, Mrs. J.
    - Negatives (Box FB098)
    - Negatives (Box FB099)
  - Ellington, Douglas D. (Chunn's Cove, Ashville, NC)
    - Negatives (Box FB018)
  - Elman, Hodja (Mischa Elman's daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB099)
  - Elman, Mischa
    - Negatives (Box FB099)
    - Negatives (Box FB100)
  - Elman, Mischa (children Nadia and Joseph), 1932
    - Negatives (Box FB100)
  - Elsmith, Mr. Leonard
    - Negatives (Box FB018)
  - Emerson, Mrs. Frederick
    - Negatives (Box FB018)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Englebert, Henri
    - Negatives (Box FB018)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Erdman, Haris
    - Negatives (Box FB100)
  - Erdwan, Dr. Charles R., 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
  - Erikson, Phoebe, 1959
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Estabrook, Rev.
    - Negatives (Box FB100)
  - Estabrook, Rossetta
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - Estabrook, Rossetta (nephew)
    - Negatives (Box FB100)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Eugene, Prince of Sweden, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
  - Evrenoff, ---- [likely Nikolai Evreinov, Moscow Art Theatre]
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
  - F-----, Mrs William (grandchildren)
    - Negatives (Box FB100)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Fairbanks, Mr. John M. (daughter Ann), 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
  - Falkman, Mr. and Mrs. Oscar (Stockholm, Sweden)
    - Negatives (Box FB100)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Far West (for Pleycer)
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
  - Farmer, Henry and Jean (children of Mrs. Henry Farmer)
    - Negatives (Box FB101)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Farmer, Mrs. Henry
    - Negatives (Box FB101)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Farmer, Mrs. Henry (daughter[?] Janet)
    - Negatives (Box FB101)
    - Negatives (Box FB102)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Farmsworth, Dr. Charles
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
  - Farmsworth, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
  - Farmworth, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB188)
  - Favrot, Mrs. Clifford
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
  - Fazio, Mr. Peter U., 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
  - Fenner, Phyllis
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
  - Fenton, General Chauncey L.
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Fernandés, Sarah (Hampton)
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
  - Finan, Miss Leilia M. (Barnard College Physical Ed.)
    - Negatives (Box FB102)
  - Finley, Dr. John, 1940
    - Negatives (Box FB102)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives, 1938 (Box FB102)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield; also studio in Manchester, 1937
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - Fisher, Welthy (L.P.C.), 1963
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - Fisk, Amanda (niece of Halen Bradley)
    - Negatives (Box FB102)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Fisk, Mrs. Charles J.
    - Negatives (Box FB102)
  - Fitts, Miss Ada M.
    - Negatives (Box FB102)
  - Flanders (children of Mrs. R.E.)
    - Negatives (Box FB188)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Flanders, Mr. and Mrs. Ralph, 1961
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Flanders, Mr. and Mrs. Ralph (daughter of Mrs. Clement Ford)
    - Negatives (Box FB102)
    - Negatives (Box FB103)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Flanders, Mrs. Ralph
    - Negatives (Box FB019)
  - Flanders, Mrs. Ralph at wedding of Jimmie
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
  - Flanders, Mrs. Ralph and Nancy
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Flanders, Mrs. Ralph and son
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Flanders, Ralph, 1961
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
  - Fletcher, Fanny
    - Negatives (Box FB103)
  - Flint, Lillian, 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
  - Flood, Mrs. M. [?]
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Flook, Mrs. William M.
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Flynt, Perry (daughter of Mrs. Robert Flynt)
    - Negatives (Box FB103)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Fogle, Bryce
    - Negatives (Box FB105)
    - Negatives (Box FB106)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Fokine, Michel
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - Folinsbee, John, 1952
    - Negatives (Box FB103)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Ford, Mrs. Clement, 1927
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
    - Negatives (Box FB104)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Ford, Ellen and Martha
    - Negatives (Box FB103)
    - Negatives (Box FB104)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Ford, ---- (daughter of Mrs. Clement Ford)
    - Negatives (Box FB103)
  - Ford, Kyo[?] (daughter of Mrs. Clement Ford), 1943
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
  - Ford, Phyllis
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Forrer, Anita
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Forsyth, Mrs. Holmes, 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Foster, ---- (son and daughter, unmarried)
    - Negatives (Box FB104)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Foster, Jeanne R. (Scotia), 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB020)
  - Foster, Jessica
    - Negatives (Box FB104)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Foster, Mr. and Mrs. D.L. with baby, 1937
    - Negatives (Box FB104)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Foster, Mr. H.L. (Wells, VT)
    - Negatives (Box FB104)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Foster, Mrs. (daughter in law)
    - Negatives (Box FB104)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Foster, Mrs. H.C.
    - Negatives (Box FB104)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Fowle, Curtis
    - Negatives (Box FB104)
  - Fowle, Farnsworth Curtis
    - Negatives (Box FB104)
  - Fowle, Luther
    - Negatives (Box FB105)
  - Fowle, Luther and family, 1924
    - Negatives (Box FB188)
  - Fowle, Mrs Luther (children)
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Fowles, James and family
    - Negatives (Box FB105)
  - Fowles, James and family, 1964
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
  - Fowles, James (brother in law and family), 1955
    - Negatives (Box FB105)
  - Frankfurter, Felix
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
  - French, Mrs. John, 1938
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Friedfeldt, Capt. Louis
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Friedman, Peter (son of Mrs. Ralph Friedman)
    - Negatives (Box FB105)
  - Fries, Deana (daughter of Mrs. August Fries)
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Frost, Barbara (daughter of Mr. and Mrs. F.G. Frost), 1939
    - Negatives (Box FB105)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Frost, Mrs. (mother of Henry S. Beal)
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
  - Frost, Robert
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Frost, Ruggles
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Fry, Lois (niece of Beatrice Gordon-Smith)
    See also Gordon-Smith, Beatrice (niece's wedding).
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
    - Negatives (Box FB105)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Fuguet, Mrs. William D., 1960
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Fullam, Mrs. Eban Joel, and Dr. & Mrs. Bryant
    - Negatives (Box FB188)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Fuller, Edmund, 1969
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
  - Fuller, Mrs. Erford C. (Aspinwald?)
    - Negatives (Box FB105)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Furay, ---- (grandchildren)
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Furay, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Gabahan, Halen, and Tamara Deykarhanova
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
  - Gabney, Mary J.
    - Negatives (Box FB106)
  - Gade, August and family, and sister of Grace McCrady
    See also McCrady, Grace.
    - Negatives (Box FB106)
  - Gadsby, Mrs., 1965
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB021)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Gal [?], 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB022)
  - Gallaher, Mr. Hugh (daughter Elizabeth)
    - Negatives (Box FB106)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Gane, Marguerite, 1960
    - Negatives (Box FB022)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Gane, Mrs. Paul and 2 children, and Mrs. Wehrbahne's niece
    - Negatives (Box FB106)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Garrett, Eileen, 1941
    - Negatives (Box FB022)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Garrison, ----, 1964
    - Negatives (Box FB022)
  - Gascoigne, Mrs. Richard T., 1957
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box FB022)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
  - Gates, -----, 1971
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB022)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
  - Gates, Mrs. Harold E.
    - Negatives (Box FB022)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Gates, Mrs. Harold E. and John and Lois
    - Negatives (Box FB022)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
  - Geofatb [?]
    - Negatives (Box FB106)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Georgia: Savannah
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB106)
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
    - Negatives (Box FB172)
  - Gerdan, -----, 1931
    - Negatives (Box FB022)
    - Negatives (Box FB106)
    - Negatives (Box FB107)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Gerdan, Carl & Mrs. and family, 1936
    - Negatives (Box FB107)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Gerdan, Carl and group (1 early group, others in N.Y.), 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB107)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Gerdan, Mrs. Carl, 1934
    - Negatives (Box FB023)
    - Negatives (Box FB107)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Gerdan, Mrs. Carl and children, 1933
    - Negatives (Box FB023)
    - Proof prints (Box 77)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Gerdan, Mrs. Carl and Sondra Carlson
    - Negatives (Box FB023)
  - Gerdan, Sondra (daughter of Mrs. Carl Gerdan), 1932
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Gerdan, Mrs. Carl (8 children), 1935
    - Negatives (Box FB107)
    - Proof prints (Box 82)
  - Gerdan Estate